simpleviewcrm.com 2012-06-06

# simpleview | Destination Marketing Solutions | CVB Tourism Software

**simple** view, inc. values your privacy. That's why we're doing everything we can to protect your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains what personal information we collect, what we do with it, what we don't do with it, and how we keep it safe. By visiting this website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

[www.simpleviewinc.com](http://www.simpleviewinc.com/) is the official web site of simpleview, inc. Our postal address is 7458 North La Cholla Blvd., Suite 100 Tucson, Arizona, 85741. We can be reached via e-mail at [info@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:info@simpleviewinc.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 520-575-1151.

We are committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining your trust. We have created the following privacy policy to explain our processes and express this commitment.

We do not collect any personal information except that knowingly and willingly supplied by the visitor. We collect the domain name from each visitor as well as statistical information such as the number of visitors and the pages viewed. Personal identifying information may be collected through e-newsletter lists, mailing lists, online request forms, contests, feedback forms, surveys, and personal interest forms. Any information that the customer provides, such as name, address, e-mail, ZIP code, gender, and income will be stored in a secure location and will be used only for those purposes for which it was given.

The information that we collect is used to enhance the usability and improve the content of our web page. It may be used to personalize information and for statistical purposes. Personal information will not be shared with third parties unless otherwise indicated or unless required to do so by law. [www.simpleviewinc.com](http://www.simpleviewinc.com/) contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the information collection processes on these sites and cannot control how the information is used.

We reserve the right to change and update our privacy policy. Any changes to our policy will be posted on this site. Last Updated: May 8, 2008
